Man, it's freezing.
How long are they going
at it today? Jeez...
I haven't eaten anything since
this morning. I'm starving.
What should I eat when I get home?
Huh? But I told you bigger was better.
If we're going to make it fight,
heavier is the best choice.
Oh, then go find it and call back later.
Hmm? He's gone?
Did he go somewhere?
Man, what a pain. Bathroom break?
Hey, look!
Think it eats fish sausage?
Wait, that thing was in the
tournament, wasn't it?
Here you go. It's fish sausage.
Come on, pandas don't meat, you know.
It's tasty.
It's bamboo. They eat bamboo.
I'll take the fish sausage.
No cameras on the emergency stairs!
Yo!
Panda-senpai, are you really sure?
This could cause you trouble later.
It's fine, it's fine!
Let's secure the area near the door.
Gah! Kirara!
Why isn't Kirara with Hakari?!
Panda-chan?
And... that spiky-haired kid.
If Panda-chan helped him
sneak in here, that means...
he's with Jujutsu High?
That means Yu-chan is
with Jujutsu High, too!
Kin-chan's in danger!
Boss, I need to—
Demon Dogs: Totality!
Hop!
Fushiguro?!
My Demon Dog was thrown back?!
No, judging from what Panda-senpai
said, it couldn't get close!
I've already marked Panda-chan.
The monitor room!
Kirara's planning to head back to Hakari!
Wait, Kirara!
We're not your enemies!
We just want to ask Hakari for a favor!
I don't believe you!
I'm disappointed in you, Panda-chan!
Oh, I can't get close to you, either!
Ow!
So Kirara-san can't get
close to us, either?
Fushiguro?!
It's more than just being unable
to approach Kirara-san.
I can't separate from Demon Dogs, either?!
What kind of cursed technique is this?!
Listen to me!
No way!
My passion's gone cold now!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Episode 53
Cog
We're in a stalemate.
Perfect.
Kirara-san!
We're not actually with
Jujutsu High right now!
You know what Tokyo is
like now, don't you?
The barriers that sprung up in
each region are related, too.
It was an unprecedented attack
of jujutsu terrorism!
We need Hakari-san's help!
You all are the ones
who excluded us first.
You reap what you sow.
I told you, we're not with Jujutsu High!
What happened between
you and the higher-ups?
They fought with the conservatives.
Their idea of "conservative" goes beyond
just their policy toward the regulations.
They have set ideas of
what jujutsu should be.
Kugisaki's technique is a good example.
That's the kind of classic
jujutsu the conservatives like.
Not stuff like the cursed videos
that were popular a while back.
As time goes on, even jujutsu
incorporates more new technologies.
But when even techniques
start doing that,
the conservatives get fussy.
Kin-chan's technique
is a perfect example.
Those stupid higher-ups lost
because they're like that.
But you all can always have
Satoru Gojo wipe your asses, can't you?
I don't understand why
you need to rely on us.
So obviously I'd assume that means
you're lying about relying on us,
and you're here for
some other reason, right?
Gojo-sensei was sealed.
That's why we lost.
They don't believe us!
Well, I can understand that.
But this person is the one
closest to Hakari-san!
Fleeing Hares!
Bunnies?
If we can convince them,
negotiations with Hakari-san
will go more smoothly!
Acrux?!
Gacrux?!
What an incredible amount.
What is he up to?
My technique marks cursed energy,
so it treats sorcerers and their
shikigami as one in the same.
At this rate, they'll just be
drawn to him like that doggy was,
and he'll be crushed under his own
shikigami until he suffocates.
Panda-senpai!
How was Fleeing Hares?!
They were second to me in cuteness!
I'm asking you what they were
and weren't able to approach!
Oh.
They were able to come to me and
that second floor no problem!
They couldn't get near Kirara and
the door to the monitor room!
Panda-senpai, do you have a star
and a name somewhere on your body?
Huh?
Oh!
I-M-A-I?
One should be somewhere on me...
Ima? Ima? Imai?
There!
It says "Imai"!
It's "Acrux," like on the Fleeing Hares!
It's probably on Demon Dogs, too.
I still don't know anything
about it, but I should...
I got it!
This technique is based
on a constellation!
People familiar with them
could figure that out.
The constellation it's based on is...
the Southern Cross!
Shit!
We both let it show on our faces!
Seriously?
His look said, "Seriously?!"
He wasn't certain my technique
was based on the Southern Cross!
But I also gave him the same look!
I confirmed it for him!
If he figures out any
more of my technique,
he'll be able to enter the monitor room!
I have to stop him here!
Back in a stalemate again?
Still, it really was the Southern Cross?
I'm grateful to Tsumiki.
I don't know anything else, though.
Also, wasn't the Southern Cross
a four-star constellation?
Fushiguro!
I really can get close to Panda-senpai.
Senpai, the Southern Cross
has four stars, right?
Huh?
Well, it is a cross.
Yeah, I guess so.
Kirara-san's technique applies one of the
stars in the Southern Cross to each of us,
and I thought it might use that to force
us to maintain a certain distance.
But Kirara-san can approach the door,
and you and I can approach each other.
Maybe it's just that Kirara and the
door's stars are repelling ours?
"Cross Theory"
If that were true,
it would make more sense for Kirara-san
to flee into the monitor room.
Oh, true.
If they hugged the inside of
the door, we'd be stuck.
Then what about this?
Star A is able to approach Star B,
but B can't approach A.
Each Star has one they're compatible with,
and they can only approach that one.
"Rock-Paper-Scissors Theory"
Like in rock-paper-scissors.
But you and I can approach
each other and move freely.
So that's not it, then.
I think it's like a stamp rally,
where you have to follow a set route
and approach each one in order.
And things with the same
star get drawn together.
"Stamp Rally Theory"
I see.
But what if the sorcerer
isn't counted as a target?
That can't be the case.
They were forced to stay
away from Demon Dogs, too.
Right now, Kirara-san is wary
of us fulfilling some kind of condition
out of their sight that's needed
to enter the monitor room.
Then there are five or more stars.
Right.
If my stamp rally theory is correct,
then we should be able to approach
Kirara-san if there are only four stars.
So there has to be a fifth star
that we have to pass through in order
to reach Kirara-san and the door.
What if there are six or seven stars?
I'd like to believe that's not the case.
It's already confusing that there
would be five stars in a cross.
If they've figured it out,
then I have to attack!
Panda-senpai!
I'm okay!
Don't worry about me!
Fushiguro! Find the star!
Hey! You can't throw it!
Huh?
They put the same Imai star on that car!
If you throw it, it'll just come back
or pull you toward it
like Demon Dogs did to me!
They probably have to touch
the target to plant a star.
But Kirara-san hasn't touched
me or Fleeing Hares.
She only touched Demon Dogs.
Meaning Kirara-san is tagging
cursed energy, not objects!
In order to tag doors and cars,
they should need someone to imbue cursed
energy into them ahead of time.
I knew it!
The car has residual cursed
energy from someone else!
If the technique doesn't
cover a wide range,
then traces of the other
star should be...
There!
The fifth star!
I don't see any more residuals
from someone other than us.
Kirara-san's already marked
their own cursed energy,
so they can't use their
own cursed energy
to mark objects with the same
Acrux star they gave me.
Meaning they can't launch things
at me like they did with that car!
Once I touch that,
I can approach Kirara-san!
Fushiguro's hypothesis was correct.
Kirara's cursed technique,
Love Rendezvous,
apportions five stars to targets' cursed
energy with the Southern Cross as a base.
For one star to approach another,
it must follow a predetermined order,
and things marked with the
same star attract each other.
You're incredible.
You actually figured out my technique.
Panda-senpai!
That order was nearest
to the farthest star.
Constellations may look flat,
but they do, of course, have depth,
and each star has a different
distance from Earth.
But since you're too smart,
you decided I could no longer
throw objects at you, didn't you?
I can just lift the Ginan star
placed on my own cursed energy
and mark things with the same
Acrux star that's on you!
What?!
How?! Where did it come from?!
No, that's it! That boy...
never dismissed his doggy shikigami!
Did he figure out which of
the same tagged objects
would be drawn to the other?!
Then he put a wall between
himself and the shikigami
so the shikigami would
be drawn into the wall,
and unleashed the doggy when
I was in a line between them!
Love Rendezvous, cancel!
Please hear us out.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Did you really set that up on purpose?
You couldn't have known if you or the
doggy would get pulled toward the other.
I took a gamble, but now I'm certain.
The one with greater cursed energy
pulls the other toward it, right?
The first time, I was
pulled into Demon Dogs,
but when I strengthened my cursed
energy to guard against your attack,
the opposite happened.
Are you really a first-year?
You really aren't cute at all.
Please. We don't have time.
Please hear us out.
Fine.
Itadori?!
Fushiguro, Panda-senpai...
Stay out of this!
Underestimating me, huh?
Straight to the face!
This brat! He's not...
even trying to dodge!
You're crazy.
This isn't like the fight in Shibuya.
This is basically a ritual
to make Hakari-senpai
acknowledge me.
I won't dodge anymore.
I won't fight back.
Not until he caves.
Interesting! I'll listen to you...
for as long as you remain standing!
Kin-chan!
These kids just want your help!
Hear them out!
I just said I would!
So, Itadori, why me?
This is the first time we've met, right?
So why rely on me?
Because my senpai
all said you're strong.
Figures.
Whenever a sorcerer asks
another sorcerer for help,
it's understood they're asking
him to risk his life with them!
So you have to show me you have
passion worth risking my life for!
Right here and now!
Yet you're telling me you came
here on orders without that?
What the hell was old man Yaga thinking?!
He should be weeding out losers like you!
I don't have any passion.
Huh?
I'm a cog.
A cog in the machine that sorcerers
need to keep exorcising curses.
Wait, wait, wait. Are you for real?
That's super disappointing.
This is bad! Itadori, that's enough!
Hurts, doesn't it?
According to Gojo-san,
my cursed energy's coarser and
grittier than that of others.
You dead?
Hey, Panda!
Sea Urchin Head!
Take Itadori and get lost already.
Don't come ba—
Huh?!
He took three unguarded blows!
And I punched him a
bunch before then, too!
What are you made of?
I'm a cog.
Cogs have a function, you know.
My function is to keep exorcising curses.
If you're necessary to achieve that,
then I'll play along
until you agree to it.
Senpai.
What is your function?
This kid...
So this is a cog's passion?
Fine. I'll keep punching—
Kin-chan.
He's gotten you heated up, hasn't he?
Passion never lies.
Get down here, you three.
Huh?
Let's cut a deal.
Huh? It's resolved?
Did you just convince him?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
We may hate the upper brass,
but Kin-chan always burned hottest when
he was helping others at Jujutsu High.
Ow!
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong,
ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong!
What?!
A Player has added a new
rule to the Culling Game!
Rule 9: Players shall be able to view the
following information on other players:
name, points, number of
rules added, current Colony.
8: Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days of
joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
9: Players shall be able to view the
following information on other players:
name, points, number of
rules added, current Colony.
You have gained five points.
Damn right. I killed him.
Every one of these guys is too weak.
It was better 400 years ago.
Where are you, Sukuna?
You have exceeded 200 points.
Would you like to consume 100 points
to add a rule to the Culling Game?
Right, the rules.
If I knew their names, and points
would demonstrate their strength...
Oh, but points go down
when adding a rule.
So I'd need the number
of rules they added, too.
And also which colony they're in.
Kogane.
Add a rule.
Reveal that information for every player.
Culling Game Player Hajime Kashimo
You're in the space between
dreams and reality.
It's a curse.
How do you know my name?
I'm not like Itadori.
Once you step inside,
you, too, become a Player!
...and make them add a rule to let
Tsumiki escape the Culling Game!
Next Episode
Tokyo Colony No. 1